it is such a crisis. There are so many children who are hurt and have no parents to help them
that there's a new term that the Palestinian community and the international community is
now using. Tell us what that term is to describe these children. Yeah. And actually, when you said
that, it gave me chills, like I'm about to say it, right? That term is from Doctors Without
Borders, who have been operating in Gaza for the last two years. It's WCNSF. That stands for
Wounded Child, No Surviving Family. That phrase didn't really exist before the last two years.
Wounded Child, No Surviving Family. Wounded Child, No Surviving Family. Okay. So that group of
children is who we are here for today. That is, those children are who we as the pod squad are
going to show up for now in this moment. The children who are wounded children with no surviving
family. One of our operating principles is that there is no such thing as other people's children,
children, which means there is in some sense surviving family, and that is us.